<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>content on A Hugo website</title><link>https://woodwirk.github.io/hugo-beryllium/tags/content/</link><description>Recent content in content on A Hugo website</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://woodwirk.github.io/hugo-beryllium/tags/content/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>04 - Advanced - Make a website with Hugo</title><link>https://woodwirk.github.io/hugo-beryllium/features/recipe-examples/advanced/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woodwirk.github.io/hugo-beryllium/features/recipe-examples/advanced/</guid><description>Instructions Install a version of Hugo on your computer Install git (or download a Hugo theme directly) Follow the Hugo quickstart guide or the setup on the About page If you&amp;rsquo;re not using the git submodule approach, you will need to adapt the quickstart to your configuration. If you don&amp;rsquo;t want to use the hugo terminal commands, you can also create text file content directly. A photo from Pexels, in the public domain.</description></item><item><title>Excluding content</title><link>https://woodwirk.github.io/hugo-beryllium/hugo-usage/excluding-content/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woodwirk.github.io/hugo-beryllium/hugo-usage/excluding-content/</guid><description>If you want to exclude files, here are a few methods:
(Probably best approach) Use a headless bundle. The easiest way to do this is to make a new folder, move the content you want to hide, and create an index.md file in that folder. Make sure to include the headless parameter in the front matter, and set it to true. This allows you to keep your content organized in your notes, and you can separate working files (which may include markdown) from the content that shows on the site.</description></item><item><title>Pages in Hugo</title><link>https://woodwirk.github.io/hugo-beryllium/hugo-usage/page-bundles/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woodwirk.github.io/hugo-beryllium/hugo-usage/page-bundles/</guid><description>There are three main ways to make content for this site:
Loose Markdown (.md) files Leaf bundles Branch bundles Loose Markdown files This is probably the easiest method, and it works well if you don&amp;rsquo;t need to associate it with images or other files. You just write markdown, call the file whatever you want, put it in a folder, and you&amp;rsquo;re done. You can still include images, videos, and so on from online sources or the /static/ folder in your website files.</description></item></channel></rss>