<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Theme settings on A Hugo website</title><link>https://woodwirk.github.io/hugo-beryllium/features/theme-info/</link><description>Recent content in Theme settings on A Hugo website</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://woodwirk.github.io/hugo-beryllium/features/theme-info/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>`config.toml` settings</title><link>https://woodwirk.github.io/hugo-beryllium/features/theme-info/settings/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woodwirk.github.io/hugo-beryllium/features/theme-info/settings/</guid><description>Site title The site title will usually appear in the tab of your web browser, next to the page title.
title = &amp;quot;A Hugo website&amp;quot;
Base URL baseurl or baseURL
If building for GitHub pages, you may need to specify the full URL for baseurl (e.g. https://woodwirk.github.io/hugo-beryllium/).
If building for another service, like AWS, you may be able to just use baseurl = &amp;quot;/&amp;quot;
Menu items Site description Edit the metadata site description under the params list.</description></item><item><title>File structure</title><link>https://woodwirk.github.io/hugo-beryllium/features/theme-info/structure/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woodwirk.github.io/hugo-beryllium/features/theme-info/structure/</guid><description>Folders and files By default, all folders with content (sections) will show up on the home page grid. Sub-folders (sub-sections) will appear for each section page, unless a different layout is specified.
Typically a section or branch bundle is made and identified by adding an _index.md file.
Content Content files are typically index.md or content-name.md. For more info on Hugo content in general, see here.
Content files are typically written in Markdown and include front matter to indicate the title and other metadata.</description></item><item><title>Front matter parameters</title><link>https://woodwirk.github.io/hugo-beryllium/features/theme-info/front-matter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woodwirk.github.io/hugo-beryllium/features/theme-info/front-matter/</guid><description>force_toc Force a table of contents to appear. Otherwise, TOC appears only for content longer than 400 words when toc is enabled.
Usage toc: true
force_toc: true # or false
refs List references in the front matter, and they will appear at the bottom of the page, after the main content. The template is included in list-title, list, recipe, single (default) layouts. It is supplied as a partial, so it can be included in other layouts.</description></item><item><title>Layouts</title><link>https://woodwirk.github.io/hugo-beryllium/features/theme-info/layouts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woodwirk.github.io/hugo-beryllium/features/theme-info/layouts/</guid><description>about Includes content, if it is present, and all taxonomy terms. Taxonomy terms are listed by section and arranged into a grid of squares.
home Includes section links in square grid layout. Below the sections, recent content is included. The date can be configured in the site settings.
single The default layout for content pages. Includes key points at the top, references at the bottom, and a list of tags associated with the page.</description></item></channel></rss>