<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>hugo-features on A Hugo website</title><link>https://woodwirk.github.io/hugo-beryllium/tags/hugo-features/</link><description>Recent content in hugo-features on A Hugo website</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://woodwirk.github.io/hugo-beryllium/tags/hugo-features/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Using Hugo</title><link>https://woodwirk.github.io/hugo-beryllium/hugo-usage/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woodwirk.github.io/hugo-beryllium/hugo-usage/</guid><description>This content discusses some simple features of Hugo.
For example, this is a list page (for a section). It provides and introduction to the following content, then lists content in this folder and subfolders.
When in doubt, refer to the docs!</description></item><item><title>04 - Advanced - Make a website with Hugo</title><link>https://woodwirk.github.io/hugo-beryllium/features/recipe-examples/advanced/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woodwirk.github.io/hugo-beryllium/features/recipe-examples/advanced/</guid><description>Instructions Install a version of Hugo on your computer Install git (or download a Hugo theme directly) Follow the Hugo quickstart guide or the setup on the About page If you&amp;rsquo;re not using the git submodule approach, you will need to adapt the quickstart to your configuration. If you don&amp;rsquo;t want to use the hugo terminal commands, you can also create text file content directly. A photo from Pexels, in the public domain.</description></item><item><title>Taxonomies in Hugo</title><link>https://woodwirk.github.io/hugo-beryllium/hugo-usage/taxonomy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woodwirk.github.io/hugo-beryllium/hugo-usage/taxonomy/</guid><description>One way to organize the content in your notes and on the site is though taxonomies like tags and categories. This site will automatically show all of your taxonomy terms on the about page.
By default, Hugo uses tags and categories. If you want to use custom terms to organize your site, define your own terms in the format:
singular_taxonomy_term = 'front_matter_term'
Then edit the config.toml file to include a section like the following.</description></item><item><title>Excluding content</title><link>https://woodwirk.github.io/hugo-beryllium/hugo-usage/excluding-content/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woodwirk.github.io/hugo-beryllium/hugo-usage/excluding-content/</guid><description>If you want to exclude files, here are a few methods:
(Probably best approach) Use a headless bundle. The easiest way to do this is to make a new folder, move the content you want to hide, and create an index.md file in that folder. Make sure to include the headless parameter in the front matter, and set it to true. This allows you to keep your content organized in your notes, and you can separate working files (which may include markdown) from the content that shows on the site.</description></item><item><title>Front Matter</title><link>https://woodwirk.github.io/hugo-beryllium/hugo-usage/front-matter/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woodwirk.github.io/hugo-beryllium/hugo-usage/front-matter/</guid><description>Front matter should be the first thing you add to a plain text file for this site, and it&amp;rsquo;s how you set the title of a page, date, authors, and taxonomy information like categories and tags. It&amp;rsquo;s required1 for the content pages of your website, and it&amp;rsquo;s also useful for organizing your notes offline.
This theme includes some custom front matter options described in the features section. Here&amp;rsquo;s an example:</description></item><item><title>Pages in Hugo</title><link>https://woodwirk.github.io/hugo-beryllium/hugo-usage/page-bundles/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woodwirk.github.io/hugo-beryllium/hugo-usage/page-bundles/</guid><description>There are three main ways to make content for this site:
Loose Markdown (.md) files Leaf bundles Branch bundles Loose Markdown files This is probably the easiest method, and it works well if you don&amp;rsquo;t need to associate it with images or other files. You just write markdown, call the file whatever you want, put it in a folder, and you&amp;rsquo;re done. You can still include images, videos, and so on from online sources or the /static/ folder in your website files.</description></item></channel></rss>