<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Theme-infos on A Hugo website</title><link>https://woodwirk.github.io/hugo-beryllium/theme-info/</link><description>Recent content in Theme-infos on A Hugo website</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://woodwirk.github.io/hugo-beryllium/theme-info/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>`config.toml` settings</title><link>https://woodwirk.github.io/hugo-beryllium/theme-info/settings/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woodwirk.github.io/hugo-beryllium/theme-info/settings/</guid><description>Site-wide configuration Taxonomy terms Hugo uses tags and categories as the default taxonomy terms. The search functionality has been configured to comb through any defined taxonomy terms, in addition to site content.
See more info on the example site and official documentation.
[taxonomies] category = &amp;#39;categories&amp;#39; tag = &amp;#39;tags&amp;#39; author = &amp;#39;author&amp;#39; Taxonomy color To set the background color of the link squares, supply a HEX color in the configuration file.</description></item><item><title>File structure</title><link>https://woodwirk.github.io/hugo-beryllium/theme-info/structure/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woodwirk.github.io/hugo-beryllium/theme-info/structure/</guid><description>Folders By default, all folders with content (sections) will show up on the home page grid. Sub-folders (sub-sections) will appear for each section page.
Content See the example site&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Hugo Usage&amp;rdquo; page or Hugo&amp;rsquo;s documentation of page bundles for content organization.
Photos, audio, and PDF media are supported, as demonstrated in the example site media-examples folder.
If pages aren&amp;rsquo;t showing at all on the site, check that the page you want to publish is not a draft.</description></item><item><title>Layouts</title><link>https://woodwirk.github.io/hugo-beryllium/theme-info/layouts/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woodwirk.github.io/hugo-beryllium/theme-info/layouts/</guid><description>Apply a layout by specifying the layout name in the front matter. Certain layouts will be automatically applied, according to Hugo&amp;rsquo;s conventions.
About Includes content, if it is present, and all taxonomy terms, by section.
Recipe Manually applied.
layout: recipe
Includes components in a sidebar and content in a main panel.
There are three styles of recipe layouts, as shown by the different front matter organization in the recipe examples.</description></item></channel></rss>